The Vagabond in the Sky
W-What the heck is going on here?!
Have you also been sealed by the Metal Breath?
No.
I see you desire freedom too, just like me.
Nice to meet y-
You dare compare me to the likes of you? Don't make me laugh!
I will soon be the king of the Metal Cardbots!
I see no reason to fight with an unsealed Metal Cardbot.
I will be back for the Metal Breath.
So be prepared!
Wait up!
This is all your fault!
You are too weak to be the owner of the Metal Breath!
You're the reason why Blue Cop was defeated!
I think you've gone too far, Wild Guardy.
Crest?
Jun. You said the Metal Breath was a token of friendship.
Yes. It is.
If you are truly united in your friendship, you'll be able to seal Fleta Z.
Then, you can prove what you said is true.
Wait up, Crest! I still have questions for you!
What is the deal with that guy?
In any case... what should we do with her?
...Ha, everyone, get in line... I'll sign autographs...
So you're saying you got Vera home safely?
Yeah. She didn't see that much, so I think we can make up an excuse.
And what about Crest?
We still can't reach him.
We went to his house, but it seems like he hasn't come home yet.
However... Crest knew all about the Metal Cardbots.
What?
He knew all about them but didn't say anything!
He was mocking us all this time!
We did act like we didn't know either.
I'm sure in time we'll get the chance to talk things out properly.
Jun. The emergency treatments are done.
Everyone was attacked where their defenses were weakest.
Does that mean his marksmanship is just that good?
Or maybe he knows all of our weaknesses?!
But wait! We've never even met the guy!
Yeah. I've never seen him before.
Neither have I. But I think I've heard rumors.
What kind of rumors?
Fleta Z. A wandering vagabond, going wherever the wind takes him.
Also known as the Hunter in the Wilds.
I heard he does not like to reveal himself to others, and lives alone,
enjoying the freedom it comes with.
It is said, you should be careful if you suddenly hear the sound of a flute playing.
It means that Fleta Z is aiming at you from afar.
Edo! Don't scare us!
I-I'm sorry. I was wondering if it would sound like this, haha...
Y-you don't think... he could still be lurking somewhere around here?!
He's likely looking for Jun, since he's after the Metal Breath.
But he probably doesn't even know where to find me!
Still, he's sure to try finding Jun through Vera.
Why not call her?
I don't even know her number!
I'll call her right now!
Hello?
Vera? Are you free to talk?
Where are you right now?
Why do you need to know?
Anyway, get this, Anna!
I'm going to meet the person who sent me the email!
They want to hear my full story where we won't be disturbed.
I think she's meeting with Fleta Z again!
What?
Vera! Where are you?!
Is that Jun?
Uh... the park near 7th Avenue. We agreed to meet up here.
No, I don't know why they want to meet here.
They just told me to wait here, so I'm here!
Aah! L-Look at that!
You want me to run away? Why should I do that?
Aah!
W-What's that?!
Run!
W-what's-
Huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Aah! I remember you!
You're the robot that appeared at the bus stop earlier!
Alerting all pedestrians. This is an emergency.
Please evacuate immediately!
Officer, over here! There's a robot-
H-Hey, we need to get out of here!
Get away from that thing!
That's enough, Fleta Z!
We will not let you carry on like this.
I was going to ask Ms. Vera where I might be able to find you.
But I see you showed up before I had to.
Thank you for making this easier.
Keep dreaming!
I'll never let you take the Metal Breath, got that?!
Not even if it means your friends getting hurt?!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Phoenix Fire, setup!
Block the arrows with your Water Splash!
Roger that!
What was that? It's a skill I've never seen before.
Fleta Z and the ground are all wet!
Mega Ambler, it's your turn!
Send a Forceps Shock towards the wet ground!
Got it!
Forceps Shock!
We did it!
I have no choice... but to take a strategic retreat!
What? He ran away again!
How strange.
What is it?
He was so cocky before. But so disorganized this time.
Theo? What's up? Is everything okay?
We found out Fleta Z's secret!
Fleta Z analyzed every single Cardbot video that came up on the Internet.
And he wrote comments on all of them!
"Shadow X's weakness is his propeller.
When that is under attack, his mobility decreases."
"Mega Trucker is heavily reliant on his shield.
Aim for his blind spots for an easy win."
Hm. Fleta Z is a strategic type, huh?
He analyzed the opponent first, and only fought when victory was assured.
Hm. I think I know how we can defeat Fleta Z!
Jun!
I know where Fleta Z is!
Alright! Let's go after him right now!
Do you think Jun will be able to do it?
We'll find out soon enough.
Hm?
So you managed to find me.
Fleta Z!
The Metal Breath is not some tool to take away the Metal Cardbots' freedom!
Please listen to me!
It's no use trying to talk. I will not change my mind.
I don't want to have to hurt anyone, either.
Just hand over the Metal Breath, now!
Looks like we have no choice but to fight.
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Beak Arrow!
Transform into a car and dodge it!
Got it!
How long do you plan to keep this up?
Don't worry! The real battle begins now!
Blue Cop!
Huh?!
Now! Shadow X!
What is this?!
What do you think?! A surprise attack!
Spinning Cutter!
Nice job!
Mega Ambler! Forceps Shock!
I'll make it so you can't use that bow!
Not a chance!
Come back!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Mega Power Tackle!
You have underestimated me for the last time.
Vulture Wings!
Making my analysis useless by quickly swapping each other out,
and fighting in close proximity so I can't use my arrows.
A great strategy indeed.
However.
I am strong even without the pre-analysis or my bow.
Gathering information beforehand is simply because I'm a cautious kind of person.
You may be strong.
But, I will never let you take the Metal Breath away!
I see you're a stubborn kind of person.
I became friends with the Metal Cardbots through the Metal Breath!
This is where peaceful coexistence with the people of Earth can start!
That's all very nice to hear,
but you are just controlling them as you please.
I'm not controlling anyone!
We're just working together towards a common goal!
If we work together, we can overcome any obstacle that comes our way!
Now Dexter!
Spear Thrust!
A surprise attack from underground... not bad-
Blue Cop! Let's finish this with maximum power!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
Friendship...
Working together...
I'll see if that's true.
Here we go!
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Fleta Z...
Sealed!
We did it, Jun!
Yeah! It's all thanks to you!
Hey guys...!
I'm fine over here! Don't worry about me!
Mega Trucker! Are you alright?!
Yeah... I'm okay!
Mega Trucker!!
Don't you think this is proof enough?
That Jun actually has the right to wield the Metal Breath?
I am not ready to accept him.
Haha... you're too unyielding.
Perhaps the time has come for the final judgement,
Jun.